{"questions":[
    {
       
        "topic":"it *IS* Rocket Science",
        "questions":[{
            "question": "Which major aerospace agency awarded SpaceX a contract to develop the Crew Dragon spacecraft for transporting astronauts to the International Space Station (ISS)?",
            "answer": "NASA",
            "points": 100
        },{
            "question": "Who is considered the founding father of ISRO and served as its first Chairman?",
            "answer": "Dr. Vikram Sarabhai",
            "points": 200
        },
        {
            "question": "How many IIT’S offer branch of the Aerospace engineering?",
            "answer": "5: Kanpur , Madras, Bombay, Kharagpur, Hyderabad",
            "points": 300
        },
        {"question":"Name of the historic mission conducted by NASA, that achieved the first human landing on the Moon",
        "answer": "Apollo 11",
        
            
            "points": 400
        }, 
        {
            
            "question": "Name the spacecraft which sent to study Saturn’s moon and it successfully orbit around the Saturn?",
            "answer": "cassini",
            "points": 500
        }
    ]
        
        

    },

 

    {
        "topic":"Gadgets and Gizmos",
        "questions":[{
            "question": "Which company is famous for its high-end gaming laptops and accessories, including the ROG (Republic of Gamers) brand?",
            "answer": "ASUS",
            "points": 100
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the NVIDIA graphics card series that support ray tracing technology",
            "answer": "RTX",
            "points": 200
        },
        {
            "question": "VRR stands for?",
            "answer": "Variable Refresh Rate",
            "points": 300
        },
        {
            "question": "Processor used in Samsung S23 ultra",
            "answer": "Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 2",
            "points": 400
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the next generation of computer memory?",
            "answer": "DDR6",
            "points": 500
        }
    ]

    },

    {
        "topic":"Things of Internet (ToI)",
        "questions":[{
            "question": "The Imitation Game,a 2014 period biographical thriller film, starred which famous hollywood actor ",
            "answer": "Benedict Cumberbatch",
            "points": 100
        },
        {
            "question": "Which fictional artificial intelligence serves as the main antagonist in the 'Terminator' film series",
            "answer": "Skynet",
            "points": 200
        },
        {
            "question": "Full form of JARVIS and EDITH",
            "answer": "'Just A Rather Very Intelligent System' & 'Even Dead I am the Hero'" ,
            "points": 300
        },
        {
            "question": "Franky, is one of the main characters in One Piece and the shipwright of the Straw Hat Pirates. What is his birth name?",
            "answer": "Cutty Flam",
            "points": 400
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Aishwarya Rai Bachan's character in ROBOT?",
            "answer": "Sana",
            "points": 500
        }
    ]

    },

    {   
        "topic":"Nakli Akal - AIML",
        "questions":[{
            "question": "The total number of ways in which a robot arm can move is known as\na) Functional Orientation\nb) Degrees of Freedom\nc) Dimesnsional Versatility\nd) Coordinate Geometry",
            "answer": "Degrees of freedom",
            "points": 100
        },
        {
            "question": "The imitation game was the original name of ?",
            "answer": "The Turing test",
            "points": 200
        },
        {
            
            "question": "Machines that try to imitate human intuition while handling vague information lie in the field of AI called?",
            "answer": "Fuzzy logic",
            "points": 300
        },        {
            "question": "Which company focuses on developing brain-computer interfaces and is owned by Elon Musk",
            "answer": "Neuralink",
            "points": 400
        },
        {
            "question": "How many types of recognition are there in AI?",
            "answer": "There are 3 types of recognition in AI: Biometric Identification, Content-Based Image Retrieval, Handwriting Recognition.",
            "points": 500
        }
    ]
    },
    {   
        "topic":"Yahi Zindagi Hai",
        "questions":[{
            "question": "The study of motion without regard to forces is known as?",
            "answer": "Kinematics",
            "points": 100
        },
        {
            "question": "Which engineering is the study of objects and systems in motion?",
            "answer": "Mechanical Engineering",
            "points": 200
        },
        {
            
            "question": "What is the full form of JOSAA?",
            "answer": "Joint Seat Allocation Authority",
            "points": 300
        },        {
            "question": "Chirag Falor, who secured JEE Advanced AIR 1 2020 and then went to MIT, studied under which educational institute?",
            "points": 400
        },
        {
            "question": "Imagine, we are all hogwarts students.A _____ is a magical incantation used by sorcerers to summon a sequence of enchanted beings (or objects) into existence, again and again. ",
            "answer": "loops",
            "points": 500
        }
    ]
    }
],

"teams":[
    {
        "team-name":"Champions",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Varshini",
        "participant2":"Manikanta",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },    {
        "team-name":"NOOBS",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Kshitiz Gangwar",
        "participant2":"Saksham Sharma",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },    {
        "team-name":"Tech Titans",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Hridyansh Sharma",
        "participant2":"Harshit Soni",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },    {
        "team-name":"DEADPOOL",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Pradeep Kumar",
        "participant2":"Arpit Jain",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },    {
        "team-name":"URANTICA",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Saumya",
        "participant2":"Anurag",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },
    {
        "team-name":"Taunky Cutie 3.0",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Harsh Sharma",
        "participant2":"Pradyot Soni",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },    {
        "team-name":"Team Modular",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Yanshu Patel",
        "participant2":"Ankit Mishra",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },    {
        "team-name":"Metabots",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Param Sonawane",
        "participant2":"Namra Koyani",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },    {
        "team-name":"Team 4",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Ayush",
        "participant2":"Kavya",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-to":""
    },    {
        "team-name":"BugBiters",
        "points":0,
        "participant1":"Manini",
        "participant2":"Lehari",
        "wager-amount": 0,
        "wager-answer":"",
        "wager-to": ""

    }
],

"currentStats":{
    "currQuestion": "",
    "currPoints": ""
},

"finalStats":{
    "question": "final question loololololololololo",
    "answer": "askhaklgh",
    "active": 0
},

"tieBreaker":{

}
}   
